http://www.augustana.edu/privacy

Privacy and Social Media Policy
It is the policy of Augustana College to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect through your use of our website, Augustana.edu.
Augustana College may collect information about how visitors access and use Augustana.edu and websites affiliated with the Augustana.edu domain. Except as described below, the information collected on our websites is limited to non-personally-identifiable information (NPII) and includes information such as browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. This data is used to improve website content and website management for users. From time to time, we may release NPII in the aggregate by publishing a report on trends in the use of our website.
Augustana College also collects potentially personally-identifying information such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged-in users and for users leaving comments on blogs. Augustana College only discloses logged-in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.
Gathering of personally-identifying information
Some visitors to our website choose to interact with us in ways that require us to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, visitors who comment on a blog are asked to provide a name and email address. We may collect personal information you supply when you subscribe to a newsletter, complete a form or survey, register for an event, enter a contest or provide your email address.
We do not disclose personally-identifying information to third parties other than as described below.
If you have shared personal information with Augustana, the college may use that information in some circumstances to tailor offerings and services to you, or display web content that may be of particular interest to you. In some cases, we may share this personal information with trusted vendors to understand how we might better understand and improve your experience with and interest in Augustana College. We do not sell any personally-identifying information to a third party.
The types of personal information we collect may include name, email address, phone number, street address, and correspondence with the college. Correspondence means contact by phone, mail, email or online. Augustana may collect personal information about you as well as from third parties, including trusted vendors and suppliers and related companies.
Augustana may use email tracking to improve the emails we send you. If you do not wish to participate in email tracking, you should unsubscribe from our email list. You can opt out of email from Augustana College at any time by contacting webmaster@augustana.edu.
If you do not want personal information used by us for the purposes and activities outlined above, you may opt out by setting your web browser to reject cookies when you are using our website.
Aggregated statistics
Augustana College may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its our website. We may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, we do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Augustana College uses Google Analytics for reports and analysis about the usage and browsing patterns of users of Augustana.edu. Google Analytics tracks and analyzes non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from visitors. Data collected by Google for Augustana College is owned and used only by us. For more information about how Google Analytics collects data, see the Google Analytics privacy policy at http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.
Protection of certain personally-identifying information
Augustana College discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to employees, contractors and affiliated organizations of ours that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide requested services, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. By using our website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.
We will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to employees, contractors and affiliated organizations of ours, as described above, we disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Augustana College, third parties or the public at large.
If you have supplied your email address to Augustana College, we may occasionally send you an email to tell you about news, solicit your feedback, or for other reasons. You can opt out of email from Augustana College at any time by contacting webmaster@augustana.edu.
Augustana College takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Augustana College uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of our website, and their website access preferences.
Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our website and should use their browser to remove any cookies.
We may transmit non-personally identifiable website usage information to third parties in order to show you messages from Augustana College when you visit other sites. See (http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) Google Privacy & Terms and Facebook (https://www.facebook.com/policy.php) to find out how you may choose not to have this non-personal information used.
Sites affiliated Augustana.edu
Other sites affiliated the Augustana.edu domain may have different privacy practices. If applicable, consult the privacy statement on each page.
If you have created an account with Augustana's online gift planning website, Augustana.edu/legacy, or may create an account, please see this specific Privacy Policy.
Inappropriate social media content
The Augustana College Office of Communication and Marketing will determine whether comments posted on a college social media site are inappropriate, and whether action is necessary. Complaints regarding inappropriate content should be forwarded to the Office of Communication and Marketing at webmaster@augustana.edu.
Messages that do not harm individuals or groups and are in alignment with the college's rules and values will not be taken down.
The college communications team may respond to an inappropriate or negative message in an effort to answer concerns, share facts, engage in dialogue, etc. Responding may be done publicly or privately via social media or via other communication.
Augustana College reserves the right to remove a post from a college social media site. Messages may be removed if a message interferes with an investigation, reveals confidential information, negatively impacts the reputation of people or groups, opposes the college's core values, etc.
Policy changes
Augustana College may change its Privacy and Social Media Policy from time to time, and in Augustana College's sole discretion. We encourage visitors to check this page for any changes to the Privacy and Social Media Policy.
Last updated Jan. 4, 2016
